Giorgi Abzianidze

Georgia, Tbilisi • +995555969899 • abzianidzedev@gmail.com • linkedin.com/in/giorgi-abzianidze-ab8836135

Game Developer

Experienced Front-end/Game Developer with over 5 years of experience. I specialize in developing browser games from scratch using technologies such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Canvas, and PixiJS. With a strong mathematical background, I am committed to continuous self-improvement and advancing my skills in game development and front-end technologies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

ESA Gaming · Remote Game Developer 06/2023 - Present

• Launched 4 games.

OrbitalGaming • Tbilisi Game Developer 12/2019 - 06/2023

• Launched 12 games.

FortuneJack • Tbilisi Frontend Developer 03/2019 - 12/2019

- Fixed website UI and some issues with functionality
- Built several landing pages

EDUCATION

The Faculty of Economics and Business, Tbilisi • Tbilisi

State University, Tbilisi • Tbilisi

Faculty of Informatics and Control Systems, Georgian Technical University, Tbilisi • Tbilisi

SKILLS

HTML5

• Redux

websockets

Angular

• CSS3

TypeScript

Jest

Node.js

JavaScript

• canvas

react-testing-

jQuery

React

pixi.js

library

php

LANGUAGES

English B2

Russian B1

Georgian Native Speaker